Center for Environmental Management Records UA096
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Center for Environmental Management Records
1984 -- 2000
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Center for Environmental Management
Mayer, Jean
UA096
27.15 Linear Feet 24 boxes
Arrangement
The collection is organized into six series: Subject files; Courses and workshops; Project applications, reviews, and reports; Publications; Conferences and seminars; and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
Developed by Jean Mayer in 1984, the Center for Environmental Management is an independent center concerned with the problems of hazardous and solid wastes and toxic substances.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Scope and Contents
The Center for Environmental Management Records documents the organization's history and activities. The collection consists of course-related materials, such as syllabi and registration forms; publications; reports, including project reports and soil sample reports; and subject files.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Academic Centers and Institutes; Research and Research Administration; Curriculum and Instruction -- Teaching Material
- Subject Files, 1984 -- 2000; UA096.001; 6.0 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  The series called "Subject Files" was created to encompass various sub-groups of material encountered in the collection. Among these were the office files of CEM directors and administrators, files relating to organizing the 1995 NEEC (New England Environmental Conference), files relating to TELI (Tufts Environmental Literacy Institute), UNEP (United Nations Environmental Programme), CLEAN! (Cooperation, Learning, and Environmental Awareness Now!), information on the Global Classroom project, quarterly and annual CEM reports, reports on Gute's testimony to Congress regarding CEM funding cuts, and files regarding the establishment of CEM through EPA funding. Also included are files regarding CEM events, symposiums, and collaborating environmental organizations. While there was no original order, sub-groups were maintained by prefacing original folder titles with the name of the sub-group (i.e. files related to NEEC conference were prefaced with NEEC).
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Acacia Alciuar-Warrer, 1995; UA096.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Open for research.
  - AIChE: American Institute of Chemical Engineers, 1996; UA096.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Air We Breathe, April 9 and 10, 1994; UA096.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Air We Breathe Symposium, 1994; UA096.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Albert Robbat, 1994; UA096.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Allocations Correspondence, FY94, 1994; UA096.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Ana Soto, 1994; UA096.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Annual Program Review, April 28 and 29, 1988; UA096.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1988 -- 1992; UA096.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Applications - NESTEA, 1995; UA096.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - ATSDR/GIS Workshop, Atlanta, Feb. 08~10, 1994; UA096.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Boston CAN, 1992; UA096.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Browner Letter, 1994; UA096.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Cassidy and Associates, INC., 1993; UA096.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - CEM 5 Year Plan, 1992; UA096.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - CEM 1989: Annual report and projects, UA096.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - CEM Communications Plan, June. - Sep. 1992, UA096.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - CEM Course Bulletins, 1992; UA096.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - CEM Funding, 1993; UA096.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - CEM Funding by EPA and Planning meeting correspondence, 1984 -- 1993; UA096.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - CEM Goals, 1992; UA096.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - CEM Introductory File, 1993; UA096.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - CEM Mission Statement, Draft, 1984; UA096.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - CEM New Venture Group, 1994; UA096.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - CEM Original/Continuing Funding, 1990 -- 1992; UA096.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - CEM Plan, 1992; UA096.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - CEM Plan for research, policy and education, draft., 1985; UA096.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - CEM Program Letter, 1992; UA096.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - CEM Progress Report, 1991; UA096.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - CEM Publications, 1985; UA096.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - CEM Related Material - Store Room, 1999; UA096.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - CEM - RFA, 1993; UA096.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - CEM Strategic Plan, draft outline, 1992; UA096.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - CEM Summary report, 1993; UA096.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - CEM Support letters, 1993; UA096.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - CEM, Take back letters (CEM Files), 1994; UA096.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Certificate Program, 1995 -- 1996; UA096.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Certificate Program, 1995 -- 1996; UA096.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Class syllabus, Fall 1998, UA096.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - CEM Transition, 1992 -- 1993; UA096.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Citations, 1993; UA096.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Clean, 1993 -- 1994; UA096.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Clean, 1990; UA096.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Clean, CEM Clean meeting, 1991; UA096.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Clean, CEM Clean, 1990; UA096.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Clean communicaton, acting file., 1992; UA096.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Clean environmental economics, 1992; UA096.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Clean, Greenworks (GW) Student Coordinator, 1992; UA096.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Clean, Greenworks (GW) Survey, 1992; UA096.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - Clean, Mass PIRG, 1991 -- 1992; UA096.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Clean Planning, 1992; UA096.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - Clean Planning, 1991 -- 1992; UA096.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Clean, presss clean-related, 1992; UA096.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Clean publications, 1992; UA096.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Clean recycle, 1989 -- 1990; UA096.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Clean recycling, 1991; UA096.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Clean recycling, 1990; UA096.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Clean reports and papers, 1991; UA096.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Clean writing, 1991; UA096.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Congress, 23 Question testimony, 1909 -- 1993; UA096.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Congress, House subcommittee, 1993 -- 1994; UA096.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Congress, report to Congress: Innovative uses for closed sanitary landfill sites. Draft., 1987; UA096.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Congress, report to Congress: More efficient systems for depositing waste in landfills. Draft, 1987; UA096.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Congress: Report to Congress: Utilizing municipal sewage sludge to reclaim and extend the useful lite of sanitary landfills. Draft., 1987; UA096.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Congress: testimony to Congress, 1993; UA096.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Congress: testimony to the House of Representatives, 1993 -- 1994; UA096.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Congress: testimony to the House subcommittee on VA, HUD and Independent Agences; Pathways to substainability., 1993; UA096.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Consortium, Pollution Prevention Consortium, 1994; UA096.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Continuation/Add-on, 1994; UA096.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1996; UA096.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Course requirements information sheet, 1991 -- 1992; UA096.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - CUTTINO, 1996; UA096.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - D.C. Contacts, 1994; UA096.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Diesel Fumes, 1990; UA096.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - DOD, 1992; UA096.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - DOD Reports, 1995 -- 1996; UA096.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - DOD workshop correspondents, 1996; UA096.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - EBC, 1993; UA096.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Law Institute, 1989; UA096.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Management Institute, 3rd, 5th and 8th Annual program pamphlets, 1990 -- 1995; UA096.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Environmental Management Systems seminar, 1995; UA096.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - EPA, 5 Year Application, 1992; UA096.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - EPA, 1994; UA096.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - EPA awards, 1993; UA096.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - EPA background, 1993; UA096.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - EPA funding and congress related material, 1992; UA096.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - EPA, Karen Morehouse, 1992 -- 1994; UA096.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - EPA, Loss of funding, 1994; UA096.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - EPA project funding, 1990 -- 1998; UA096.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - EPA's risk reduction Eng Lab, Oct 12-14 Cincinnati, OH, 1993; UA096.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Events, 1993; UA096.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Events, 1993; UA096.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Events, 1992; UA096.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Events, 1992; UA096.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Events calendar, 1993; UA096.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Events, Dan Damelin, 1991; UA096.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Events, Groups, 1992; UA096.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Events, miscellaneous, 1992; UA096.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Events, past events, 1993; UA096.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Executive committee, 1993; UA096.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Giampe, Rob, 1995; UA096.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Global classroom, 1989; UA096.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Gute, David, principal investigator., 1995; UA096.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Gute, David, principal investigator., 1995; UA096.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Hale, 1996; UA096.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Health, women's health and environmental hormone mimics., 1995; UA096.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Karen, Morehouse, 1994; UA096.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Loon work, 1991; UA096.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Mary Jane Shultz, 1994; UA096.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Miscelaneous writings, 1996; UA096.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Monthly projections, 1995; UA096.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - National pollution prevention center, 1995 -- 1996; UA096.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, 1993; UA096.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, 1989; UA096.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, 1995; UA096.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, 1995; UA096.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, A.D. Stone, 1995; UA096.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, 1996; UA096.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Alton Stone, 1996; UA096.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Brendan Whitaker. The religious partnership in environmental conservation., 1994; UA096.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Keith Snow. Ethics, empowerment and action, 1995; UA096.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Diane Cotman. Making ecological connections between habits and habitats., 1995; UA096.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Robert Murphy. Environmental Justice., 1995; UA096.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Amy Perry. Recycling..., 1995; UA096.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Business. Brent Blackwelder., 1995; UA096.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
    1- Gatt, Nafta, ...; 2- Economics for the Earth
  - NEEC, Ellen M. Clinton. Pollution prevention- A win-win situation, 1995; UA096.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Eric Weltman. Cabor and Toxics, 1995; UA096.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Paul Demit. Effective Stormwater Management Practices for Municipalities: Is there a role for citizen involvement, 1995; UA096.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Richard S. Hersey. Sustainable Communities in an Environmental Settings. Build your network b/f you need it., 1995; UA096.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Mattnew Wilson. Targeting industrial toxics users in your community, 1995; UA096.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Jaqueline Badders. Community business consertiums, Big opportunities in small scale recycling., 1995; UA096.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Jennifer Clifford. Economic valuation of envir. amenities, 1995; UA096.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Katherine O'Dea. The logistics engineering approach to industrial ecology., 1995; UA096.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Nancy Wrenn. Surplus paint - finding a new use for it., 1995; UA096.001.003.00043 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, David Nikki Goldbeck. Reuse: An environmental strategy with economic., 1995; UA096.001.003.00044 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Robert Charlton/ Don Maltioda. The cosmic pipe and how the pipe relates to the goals of Agenda 21., 1995; UA096.001.003.00045 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Ruth Caplan. Building a sustainable economy from the ground up., 1995; UA096.001.003.00046 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Scott Klinger. Capital Bridges: social investors and grassroots activists work together for social change., 1995; UA096.001.003.00047 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Sha-king Alston. Issues of environmental jobs, worker health and enviromental justice., 1995; UA096.001.003.00048 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Computer Docs., 1995; UA096.001.003.00049 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Daria Kronberg. Workplace giving for the environment, 1995; UA096.001.003.00050 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Database to be entered, 1995; UA096.001.003.00051 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Dr. Edward N. Aqua, 1995; UA096.001.003.00052 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Earth Day organizers. George Skillman (Earth Day track workshops), 1995; UA096.001.003.00053 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Ecological risk, Norm Richardson, 1995; UA096.001.003.00054 (Box 3)
    The folder is empty.
  - NEEC, Anne Chabot / Madaleine Ochinang. Military conversion, a changing job scene., 1995; UA096.001.003.00055 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Stephne Greene (Polaroid). Environmental regulations Hype or Hope, 1995; UA096.001.003.00056 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Annette Carson. Resisting the push to revive nuclear power: creating safe energy solutions., 1995; UA096.001.003.00057 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Veronika Thiebach. Bargaining for friendly roads, not highway, in your community., 1995; UA096.001.003.00058 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Laurie Martinelli. The Housatonic River: New Partnerships for cleaning up hazardous waste., 1995; UA096.001.003.00059 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Ed Himlan. Developing the watershed approach in Massachusetts., 1995; UA096.001.003.00060 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Michael Herz. Keeping what we've got: the role or fiver, sound and baykeepers in protecting water environments., 1995; UA096.001.003.00061 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Paul Lelito. Pits and Mounds of Wetland Protection., 1995; UA096.001.003.00062 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Ross A. Moldoff. Controlling strip development., 1995; UA096.001.003.00063 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Donald Rivard. Urban IPM and the environment., 1995; UA096.001.003.00064 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Jan P. Smith. How to minimize cumulative impacts on water resources., 1995; UA096.001.003.00065 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, William R. Taylor. Urban edible forestory or urban orchards., 1995; UA096.001.003.00066 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Ronnee Yashon. Bioethics., 1995; UA096.001.003.00067 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Emi Brochure, 1995; UA096.001.003.00068 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Janet Clark. The link between sustainable communitiesand toxic use reduction., 1995; UA096.001.003.00069 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Ana Soto. Sex under siege., 1995; UA096.001.003.00070 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Jean Lemieux. Preventing and controlling sick building syndrome through improved air quality., 1995; UA096.001.003.00071 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Mary Wishbach. How citizenz can get help with indoor air., 1995; UA096.001.003.00072 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Michael Hanauer. Exploring the role of Env. Org. in dealing with the Prob. of U.S. overpopulation., 1995; UA096.001.003.00073 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Naomi Schussler. Building coalitions for lead poisoning prevention: Regional, state, cocal models., 1995; UA096.001.003.00074 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Nicholas Ashford. MCS and the environment: A clinical perspective., 1995; UA096.001.003.00075 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Julie Wormser. 1. Strength in numbers. Building effe. coalitions. 2. Afler Cairo: The road to sustainability., 1995; UA096.001.003.00076 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Camille Vivieros. Community based action towards lead poisoning prevention., 1995; UA096.001.003.00077 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Diane Cotman. Habits and Habitats., 1995; UA096.001.003.00078 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Dr. L. K. Bharadwaj. The community, the common good, and the environment: Turning the "Bads" into the "Goods"., 1995; UA096.001.003.00079 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Mark Elbroch. Earth Skills: Reawaken your connection with the earth., 1995; UA096.001.003.00080 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Nancy W. Anderson. Agenda 21: An update on implementation progress in the USA and around the world., 1995; UA096.001.003.00081 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Richard Wetzler. Environmental literacy worldwide., 1995; UA096.001.003.00082 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Lary Rosenberg. Communicating environmental issues to the public., 1995; UA096.001.003.00083 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, management assessment., 1995; UA096.001.003.00084 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Andrea L. Jones. Working landscapes: Grassland/Heathland conservation., 1995; UA096.001.003.00085 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Neen Harmon. The northern forest: a call to action., 1995; UA096.001.003.00086 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Douglas Smith. Backyard bioengineering: Innovative solutions to watershed protection., 1995; UA096.001.003.00087 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, GDE workshops., 1995; UA096.001.003.00088 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Hank Tyler. Community lake conservation in Maine, New Hampshire and Vermont., 1995; UA096.001.003.00089 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, OSHA, Lead., 1995; UA096.001.003.00090 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, proposals., 1995; UA096.001.003.00091 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, RFP Responses Pending., 1995; UA096.001.003.00092 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, JoAnne Shatkin. Improving your inside game: A view from the trenches on effective use of the public involvement., 1995; UA096.001.003.00093 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Arthur Gladstone. Becoming more effective with personal and social obstacles to construction action., 1995; UA096.001.003.00094 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Barbara L. Baroos. City View/ Town View: Hypermapping., 1995; UA096.001.003.00095 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Susan Boyd. Community electronic networking., 1995; UA096.001.003.00096 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Lorraine Joubert. Working together within a watershed., 1995; UA096.001.003.00097 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Marshall T. Spriggs. Using comupter-based communication for the environment., 1995; UA096.001.003.00098 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Midge Taylor. Resources to help our communities come together., 1995; UA096.001.003.00099 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Richard Sutton. "Real World" uses of GIS to solve environmental problems., 1995; UA096.001.003.00100 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Ronald Kertzner. Facilitating collaborative change., 1995; UA096.001.003.00101 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Susan Schneider. Meet the press., 1995; UA096.001.003.00102 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Thomas Kelly. The role of the university in sustainable development., 1995; UA096.001.003.00103 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, Warmlines., 1995; UA096.001.003.00104 (Box 3)
  - NEEC, workshop, 1903 -- 1996; UA096.001.003.00105 (Box 3)
  - NHSRC, Northeast Haz. Substance research center., 1993; UA096.001.003.00106 (Box 3)
  - Northeast hazadous substance research center trip., 1993; UA096.001.003.00107 (Box 3)
  - Northeast Lead Initiative, 1997; UA096.001.003.00108 (Box 3)
    Community partnership program midterm meeting and community based fundraising workshop.
  - Notes from attending, 1995; UA096.001.003.00109 (Box 3)
  - Overview of campuswide programs., 1994; UA096.001.003.00110 (Box 3)
  - Peter Ofner., 1994; UA096.001.003.00111 (Box 3)
  - Pollution prevention consortion of new england universities, 1993 -- 1994; UA096.001.003.00112 (Box 3)
  - Preliminary Budget., 1996; UA096.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Program for the study of sustainable change and development, 1991 -- 1992; UA096.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Proposal, lighting implementation workshop. EPA- K. White, 1903 -- 1993; UA096.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1991; UA096.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1992; UA096.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1992; UA096.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1992; UA096.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1993; UA096.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1993; UA096.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1993; UA096.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1994; UA096.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1994; UA096.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, 1994; UA096.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Quarterly report, process for collecting documentation., 1993; UA096.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - QUEAR, Michael., 1993; UA096.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - RCC, Roxbury Community College, 1996; UA096.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Report on environmental activities at Tufts University. Draft., 1995; UA096.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Request for proposals, NHSRC and training and tech transfer., 1993; UA096.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Requests for applications., 1993 -- 1994; UA096.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Resource Room, 1992; UA096.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - RFA disks index., 1994; UA096.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - SDIN: The sustainable development inormation network., 1993; UA096.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Plan, 1992; UA096.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Strategic plan, draft., 1992; UA096.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Strategic planning, useful models., 1993; UA096.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Surendra Verma, 1994; UA096.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Teli engineering curriculum., 1994; UA096.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - TELI Executive summary., 1990; UA096.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - TELI Faculty workshop, 1994; UA096.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - TEN, 1991; UA096.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - TEN Meeting info., 1991; UA096.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - TEPC Steering committee meeting: environmental education report., 1996; UA096.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - TEPC: Tufts environmental programs council., 1993; UA096.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Tom Kelly, 1994 -- 2000; UA096.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Tufts environmental studies program: summary of program, 1993 -- 1995; UA096.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Tufts TEN Coordinator., 1990; UA096.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - UNEP Advisory committee, 1993; UA096.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - UNEP Fellows, 1990 -- 1995; UA096.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - UNEP Incident., 1993; UA096.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - UNEP Program, 1993; UA096.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - UNEP Summary, 1996; UA096.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Union Carbide, 1994; UA096.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - United States - Asia: US - AEP, 1994; UA096.001.016.00044 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - United States Council for International Business, 1994; UA096.001.016.00045 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Universidad de Chile, 1995; UA096.001.016.00046 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - University of Alaska - Fairbanks, 1994 -- 1995; UA096.001.016.00047 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - University of Amsterdam: University course on Environmental Policy, 1994; UA096.001.016.00048 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - U Conn - General, 1994 -- 1995; UA096.001.016.00049 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - University of Illinois - Chicago, 1994; UA096.001.016.00050 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - University of Massachusetts - Lowell, 1993 -- 1994; UA096.001.016.00051 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - University of Strathclyde, 1993; UA096.001.016.00052 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Vogel, Richard, 1993; UA096.001.016.00053 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Wetzler, Richard, 1993; UA096.001.016.00054 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
- Courses and workshops, 1985 -- 1995; 1987 -- 1994; UA096.002; 8.4 Linear Feet
  The series contains CEM course and workshop material (primarily from 1987 to 1994) along with general course material. The courses were held at the Medford campus of Tufts University; workshops were held off-site. The most common courses were asbestos abatement and annual review courses; CEM also taught lead abatement and radon abatement classes. The courses were offered to employees and managers in different trades. The materials include lists of those who passed the asbestos abatement classes.